

# WASEEM SAJJAD

## **About Me**

I am an experienced civil site supervisor with knowledge in construction processes, safety regulations, and project management..I have the skills to oversee construction sites, maintain high standards, and effectively lead teams. Committed to quality and safety



+92 308 8864401



wsajjad460@gmail.com



Postal Block 18, Flat A, Postal Colony G-8/4 Islamabad

### Language

- English
- Urdu

#### Hobbies

- Movies
- Cricket
- Football
- Reading

### Qualities

- Communication
- Problem Solver
- Passionate

## Objective

Results-driven Civil Engineer with a solid background in project management, structural design, and construction oversight. Proven ability to deliver high-quality projects on time and within budget. Seeking a challenging position to apply my technical expertise, leadership skills, and passion for sustainable design in contributing to the successful execution of construction projects.

## **Experience**

Husnain Builder's

Jan 2019 - Aug 2021

Site Supervisor

**Residential Project** 

Oct 2021 - Jan 2024

House Construction

### **Education**

**Matriculation** 

2015 - 2016

Islamabad College For Boys G-6/3 Islamabad

**D.A.E (Civil Engineering)** 

2017 - 2019

International Islamic University Islamabad (IIUI)

**B.Sc (Civil Eng. Technology)** 

2021 - 2024

International Islamic University Islamabad (IIUI)